

Profile

Android Developer with 3 years of experience developing high end Android Apps from scratch using modern technologies and design patterns. Currently leading a team of Android Developers in the development of a modular iGaming application suited for multiple Betting Houses and excelling at it. Committed to utilizing my skills to further the mission of a company.

Employment History

Android Team Leader, GOMA Development, Évora

AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.
- Helped the team to work better together by implementing better Git Flows and teaching modern Android design patterns.
- Structured the Android Project in order to accommodate all requirements from the stakeholders: modular features that would change according to which package the client (betting bookmakers) bought.

Android Developer, Tekever, Lisbon

MARCH 2021 - JULY 2021

- Learned a lot about security and modular applications by working at a Banking Application.
- Applied my expertise to find a way to introduce more customization to new and existing template views.
- Utilized a proprietary software developed by the company to develop features in an existing application.

Android Developer, DigitalWorks, Évora

MARCH 2019 - FEBRUARY 2021

- Received constructive criticism well and turned it into an opportunity to grow and improve.
- Operated with a strong work ethic, professionalism, and the ability to work under pressure.

Education

Bachelor Degree, Instituto Politécnico de Beja, Beja

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Developed multidisciplinary projects such as:

- Image recognition software with Python;
- Unity game;
- Pandemic simulator with Java;

Associate Degree, Instituto Politécnico de Beja, Beja

SEPTEMBER 2017 - JULY 2019

- Graduated with the best grades in the class 18/20.
- Gained deep knowledge about Web and Mobile Development and also server setup.

Details

Rua da Estalagem nro12
Beja, 7800-611
Portugal
+351965078271
rodrigoserrafernandes98@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Portfolio

Flutter Mobile Development Certificate

Web Development Bootcamp Certificate

UI, UX and Design Thinking Certificate

Skills

Kotlin

Java

Git

Flutter ReactJS

SQL

MongoDB

Languages

Portuguese

English

Spanish